Configure Flutter settings.

To remove a setting, configure it to an empty string.

The Flutter tool anonymously reports feature usage statistics and basic crash reports to help improve Flutter tools over time. See Google's privacy policy: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/

Global options:
-h, --help                  Print this usage information.
-v, --verbose               Noisy logging, including all shell commands executed.
                            If used with "--help", shows hidden options. If used with "flutter doctor", shows additional diagnostic information. (Use "-vv" to force verbose logging in those cases.)
-d, --device-id             Target device id or name (prefixes allowed).
    --version               Reports the version of this tool.
    --enable-analytics      Enable telemetry reporting each time a flutter or dart command runs.
    --disable-analytics     Disable telemetry reporting each time a flutter or dart command runs, until it is re-enabled.
    --suppress-analytics    Suppress analytics reporting for the current CLI invocation.

Usage: flutter config [arguments]
-h, --help                                     Print this usage information.
    --list                                     List all settings and their current values.
    --clear-ios-signing-settings               Clear the saved development certificate or provisioning profile choice used to sign apps for iOS device deployment.
    --select-ios-signing-settings              Complete prompt to select and save code signing settings used to sign apps for iOS device deployment.
    --android-sdk                              The Android SDK directory.
    --android-studio-dir                       The Android Studio installation directory. If unset, flutter will search for valid installations at well-known locations.
    --jdk-dir                                  The Java Development Kit (JDK) installation directory. If unset, flutter will search for one in the following order:
                                                   1) the JDK bundled with the latest installation of Android Studio,
                                                   2) the JDK found at the directory found in the JAVA_HOME environment variable, and
                                                   3) the directory containing the java binary found in the user's path.
    --build-dir=<out/>                         The relative path to override a projects build directory.
    --[no-]enable-web                          Enable or disable Flutter for web.
                                               (defaults to on)
    --[no-]enable-linux-desktop                Enable or disable support for desktop on Linux.
                                               (defaults to on)
    --[no-]enable-macos-desktop                Enable or disable support for desktop on macOS.
                                               (defaults to on)
    --[no-]enable-windows-desktop              Enable or disable support for desktop on Windows.
                                               (defaults to on)
    --[no-]enable-android                      Enable or disable Flutter for Android.
                                               (defaults to on)
    --[no-]enable-ios                          Enable or disable Flutter for iOS.
                                               (defaults to on)
    --[no-]enable-fuchsia                      Enable or disable Flutter for Fuchsia.
                                               This setting applies only to the master channel.
    --[no-]enable-custom-devices               Enable or disable early support for custom device types.
    --[no-]cli-animations                      Enable or disable animations in the command line interface.
                                               (defaults to on)
    --[no-]enable-native-assets                Enable or disable native assets compilation and bundling.
                                               (defaults to on)
    --[no-]enable-dart-data-assets             Enable or disable Dart data assets building and bundling.
                                               This setting applies only to the master channel.
    --[no-]enable-swift-package-manager        Enable or disable support for Swift Package Manager for iOS and macOS.
                                               (defaults to on)
    --[no-]omit-legacy-version-file            Enable or disable stops writing the legacy version file. If set, the file {FLUTTER_ROOT}/version is no longer written as part of the flutter tool execution; a newer file format has existed for some time in {FLUTTER_ROOT}/bin/cache/flutter.version.json.
                                               (defaults to on)
    --[no-]enable-windowing                    Enable or disable support for windowing on macOS, Linux, and Windows.
                                               This setting applies only to the master channel.
    --[no-]enable-accessibility-evaluations    Enable or disable support for accessibility evaluations.
                                               This setting applies only to the master channel.
    --[no-]enable-lldb-debugging               Enable or disable support for debugging with LLDB for physical iOS devices. If LLDB debugging is off, Xcode debugging is used instead. Only available for iOS 17 or newer devices. Requires Xcode 26 or greater.
                                               (defaults to on)
    --[no-]enable-uiscene-migration            Enable or disable support for migrating to UIScene lifecycle. If enabled, Flutter will migrate your app to iOS UIScene lifecycle if possible or otherwise instruct you to migrate manually.
                                               (defaults to on)
    --[no-]enable-riscv64                      Enable or disable support for riscv64 architecture.
    --clear-features                           Remove all configured features and restore them to the default values.

Run "flutter help" to see global options.

Analytics reporting is currently enabled.
